<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Botond Geiszt CV</title><link>https://botoxx.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Botond Geiszt CV</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://botoxx.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://botoxx.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://botoxx.github.io/about/</guid><description>DevOps Engineer with experience in cloud-native environments and automation. My studies took place at the Department of Telecommunications and Media Informatics at the Budapest University of Technology and Economics. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in cloud technologies, distributed systems, web3, and decentralized finance. I have a good understanding of cryptocurrency markets and foreign exchange. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent most of my professional career working in a cloud environment, specializing in CI/CD pipelines, automation, orchestration and infrastructure as code solutions.</description></item><item><title>Courses &amp; Certifications</title><link>https://botoxx.github.io/courses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://botoxx.github.io/courses/</guid><description> ISTQB Foundation level Software Tester Securing Kubernetes Troubleshooting Kubernetes AZ-104T00-A: Microsoft Azure Administrator Ethical Hacking, ComponentSoft ComponentSoft: OpenShift Administrator</description></item><item><title>Education</title><link>https://botoxx.github.io/education/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://botoxx.github.io/education/</guid><description>Electrical Engineer | Budapest University of Technology and Economics Department of Telecommunications and Media Informatics September 2017 - January 2022
Thesis Project: Measuring the Elasticsearch engine under load</description></item><item><title>Languages</title><link>https://botoxx.github.io/languages/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://botoxx.github.io/languages/</guid><description> Hungarian (Native) English (Fluent)</description></item><item><title>Skills</title><link>https://botoxx.github.io/skills/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://botoxx.github.io/skills/</guid><description>DevOps &amp;amp; Cloud Technologies Kubernetes, OpenShift Docker, containerization CI/CD (Jenkins, Spinnaker) Terraform, Infrastructure as Code Azure (AZ-104 certified) Helm Microservices architecture Programming Languages Python Golang Bash AI &amp;amp; Advanced Technologies AI agent building Prompt engineering Integration with Generative AI technologies Collaboration Tools Git API development Documentation systems</description></item><item><title>Work Experience</title><link>https://botoxx.github.io/experience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://botoxx.github.io/experience/</guid><description>DevOps Engineer | Ericsson, Budapest January 2022 - Present
Development and maintenance of a cloud-native Internet Multimedia Subsystem Designing, implementing, and maintaining robust and scalable CI/CD pipelines Handling trouble reports and vulnerability analysis Leveraging microservices architecture for improved system reliability Implementing Infrastructure as Code using Terraform and hybrid cloud Deployment and orchestration on Kubernetes and OpenShift environments Developing API endpoints for system monitoring and management Developer Intern | Ericsson, Budapest August 2021 - January 2022</description></item></channel></rss>